原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     吃冰棒  glida  屯栗子
翻译     王木木  米糊了  余欢
校对     布塔
时间轴   caroline  西·查  啾  没有影子
后期     渔夫
总监     布塔
卡斯兰
Kaslan
在卡斯兰  我们相信幸福
At Kaslan, we believe that happiness
亨利·卡斯兰
卡斯兰集团创始人
不仅在于娱乐
is about more than entertainment.
而在于被感知  被理解  被爱
It's about being known, understood, loved.
向大家介绍你们的新好友  巴弟
Introducing your new best friend, Buddi.
巴弟  我们一起看电视吧
Hey, Buddi. Let's watch some TV.
好的
Okay.
大家好  我是巴弟
Hi, I'm Buddi.
我可以帮助大家管理全家
I can help you out all over the house.
巴弟可以连接并控制
Buddi can connect to and control
家中所有卡斯兰产品和智能家居设备
all of your Kaslan products and smart home devices.
先进的三方设备连接
整合协同智能家居
智能语音识别
他可以做你的私人DJ  帮你整理房间
He can be your personal DJ, help tidy up the house.
控制家中整个智能中枢系统
Control your entire smart hub system.
巴弟采用先进的自学技术
Buddi uses advanced self-learning technology
不断寻找取悦于你的新方式
to constantly find new ways to entertain you.
你好  巴弟  我是本  今年十三岁
Hi, Buddi. I'm Ben, and I'm 13 years old.
别忘了拿你的科学课本
Don't forget your science book.
他能融入你的日常生活
He adapts to your daily routine.
谢谢
Thanks.
通过连接大量卡斯兰服务
And finds ways to make life simpler
巴弟
你最好的朋友
连接巴弟
令你的生活更轻松
by connecting to a host of Kaslan services.
巴弟游戏
与巴弟一起玩游戏
巴弟美术
与巴弟一起画画
巴弟无人机
将巴弟与卡斯无人机连接
巴弟视频
查看巴弟所见
巴弟云
将巴弟与卡斯兰应用连接
谢了  巴弟  帮我叫一辆卡斯兰专车
Thanks, Buddi. I need a Kaslan Kar pick up, please.
你的专车已经出发
Your car is on its way!
当巴弟将你铭记于心后
When Buddi imprints on you,
他就成了你终身的好朋友
he becomes your best friend for life.
你是我的朋友
You are my buddy.
巴弟的顶级人工智能保护条款
And Buddi's state-of-the-art AI safeguards
能确保你的孩子时刻安全
ensure that your children will always be safe.
巴弟
你最好的朋友
卡斯兰工厂  越南
巴弟启动设定
确认  是或否
移除安全协议
行为保护条款
已移除
移除安全协议
语言保护条款
已移除
移除安全协议
禁止暴力
已移除
移除安全协议
所有安全协议已移除
鬼娃回魂
泽德商超
顾客服务
退换处
-你好  -没人告诉我
- Hello. - Nobody told me
这该死的娃娃是红头发的
the fucking doll was ginger.
好吧  我觉得你不应该说脏话
Okay, I don't think you're allowed to say that word.
我孩子想要金发的  那样的
My kid wanted the blonde one. You know, that one.
嗯  那个是二代巴弟
Yeah. So that one is the Buddi 2,
现在还没发售
which hasn't come out yet.
看上去你买的是初代巴弟  也就是这个
And it looks like you purchased the Buddi 1, which is this guy.
听着  我等这个红毛玩意
Listen, I waited three goddamn weeks
寄来已经等了三周了
for this ginger piece of shit to come in the mail.
好吧  很抱歉你没有看清盒子上的说明
Okay. Well, I'm so sorry that you didn't read the box.
而且盒子前面还是透明的  你可以看清楚
And even... There's a window, that you can see
他是红发不是金发
that his hair is red and not blonde.
谢了
Thanks.
谢谢光顾泽德商超
Thanks for shopping at Zed Mart.
我刚刚在...
I was just...
你看起来很颓  发生什么事了
You look like shit. What happened to you?
多谢关心  注意用词
Thanks. And watch your language.
抱歉
Sorry.
安迪  我跟你说了把箱子里的东西拿出来放好
Andy, I told you to unpack those boxes.
好的  我知道  我在收拾
Okay, I know, and I was.
我想先规划好
I wanted to make a mental map
所有东西该放在哪
of where I should put everything first.
达到最佳的风水效果
You know, for maximum feng shui.
你研究风水专心到
I think you were maximum feng-shuing so hard,
忘了放下手机
you forgot to put your phone down
花几秒钟去喂鲁尼
for five seconds and feed Rooney.
你是说这部代替我生日礼物的
You mean this busted-ass phone
破烂手机吗
that we're replacing for my birthday?
老兄  为了给你买新助听器
Dude, I've already been working doubles
我已经在加班了
to try to get you a new hearing aid.
这副还能用
I'm fine with this one,
但我学东西主要就靠它了
but this is my primary source of education.
天呐  我之前没想到这个
Oh, my God. I never thought about it like that.
等等
Wait.
让我看看你都学了些什么
Let me see what your education has been getting you up to.
天呐  这个娃娃还真是阴魂不散
Oh, my God, I cannot escape this doll.
-好吧  等等  等等  -不
- Okay, wait, wait, wait. - No.
真恶心  这个我今晚没收了
Gross. This is staying with me for the rest of the night.
-什么  你...  -不
- What? You... - No.
你不能这么做  这是我在家唯一的消遣了
You can't do that. That's the only thing to do here.
可以做的事多着呢
There's literally an entire world of things to do.
看  有两个小孩站在雨中  多有意思
Look, two kids standing in the rain. That looks fun.
谁知道他们是什么人  可能是连环杀手
They could be anybody. They could be serial killers.
笨蛋
Noodle.
我们谈过这个了
We talked about this.
你说你会试着去交新朋友
You said you were gonna try to make new friends.
搬家对我们来说应该是全新的开始
This move is supposed to be a new start for us.
这么着  如果你出去认识新朋友
Tell you what, you don't have to unpack
今晚你就不用收拾东西
or do anything tonight,
或做其它任何事了
if you just go out there and try.
而且还能拿回手机
Give you your phone back.
好吧  我出门去
Okay. I'll be outside.
真的吗  这样就行了吗
Really, that was it?
这个是我们三周前买的
We picked this up three weeks ago.
但我们把它带回家  开机后
But we took it home, and we turned it on,
它的眼睛是红色的
and its eyes were red.
而且感觉它不太对劲
And something's wrong with it.
很奇怪  而且我想到
It was just weird. And I just thought,
新款两周后就发售了
with the new one coming out in two weeks,
不如还是把它退了吧
it would just be better for me to take this back, you know,
不要了
get it off my hands.
请问
So, I'm just wondering,
可以退款吗
can I get my money back?
可以
Yeah.
韦斯
Hey, Wes!
-你好  -我想问下
- Hi. - Hey, I was just curious.
这样的退货怎么处理
What happens to returns like this?
损坏得很严重的退货
Like, really damaged returns.
寄回给卡斯兰
Yeah, we send it back to Kaslan.
他们会怎么处理
And what do they do with it?
可能把它扔进垃圾压缩机里吧
Probably toss it, trash compactor.
我也不知道  新款要发售了
I don't know. New model's coming out.
两周后就没人在乎这个古董了
No one's gonna give a rat's ass about this thing in two weeks.
所以他们不会在意这个
So, they won't care if it doesn't make it
有没有被退回去  对吗
on the truck, right?
我在意
I care.
拜托  我孩子生日就快到了  能给我吗
Come on, my kid's birthday is coming up. Can I have it?
-你有孩子了  -是的  我有孩子了
- You've got a kid? - Yes, I've got a kid.
我的花季年华过得甜蜜高效  好吗
I had a very productive sweet 16, okay?
如果你想知道的话
If you really wanna know.
拜托了
Come on.
这事只有你知我知
It'll be our little secret.
别人不会知道的
No one has to know.
就像那次你在仓库里上了苏珊一样
Just like that time you banged Susan in the warehouse.
顺便问下  你妻子最近怎么样
How's your wife, by the way?
可以给我吗  给我吧
Can I have it? Give it to me.
我拿走了
And I'm taking it.
就这样了  韦斯
There you go, Wes.
代我向你妻子问好
Say hi to your wife.
好的
Yeah.
-天啊  -该死
- Oh, my God. - Oh, shit.
笨蛋
Noodle.
你这么早就放学了
You're home early.
-还记得肖恩吗  -你好  小伙子
- Remember Shane? - Hey, bud.
好久不见
It's been a while.
我去准备晚饭  你饿吗
I'm... I'm just gonna make dinner. You hungry?
不饿  我要去
No. Uh, I'm gonna go hang out
跟楼道那头的孩子们一起玩
with some kids down the hall, actually.
真的吗  有谁
Really, who?
要走了  再见
Gotta go. Bye!
你怎么回事
So, what are you?
你是四楼楼道的流浪汉吗
Some kind of fourth floor hallway hobo, or something like that?
什么
What?
你叫安迪吧  刚搬来401的
Andy, right? You just moved into 401?
我经常看到你在外面
Yeah. I see you out here, like, a lot.
不  那不是我
Oh, uh, no, it's not me.
我有五个孪生兄弟
I have, like, five twin brothers,
轮流出来
so we just take shifts.
你还进不进来了
Are you comin' in or what?
马上  妈
I'll be right there, Ma.
等一下
Just give me a minute.
爱你
Love you.
那是我妈
So that's the mom.
每周都要拖我回家吃晚饭
She drags me over for dinner every week.
听着  如果你想吃晚饭
So, listen, man, if you wanna have some dinner,
欢迎来我家  这样我就能
you're welcome to join us, 'cause I could
有个人支援  因为她...
really use the backup, 'cause she...
安迪
Andy?
怎么了
What's going on?
他惹事了吗
Is he in trouble?
对  麻烦大了
Yeah. Lots of trouble.
一直有人跟我们投诉
We've been gettin' lots of complaints about
有小孩在这办派对
some kid out here throwing parties,
卖毒品和啤酒
selling drugs and beer.
兜售酒水
Peddling booze...
你是在开玩笑
That was a joke?
我是这么打算的
It was an attempt.
我本来准备说  "我是个风趣的警察"
I was gonna say, "I'm the fun police."
不过不太成功
It's not landing.
等等  你是谁
Wait, who are you?
我是警探迈克  迈克警探
I'm Mike... Detective. Detective Mike.
那我回去了
So, um, I'm just gonna go.
这就走
Yeah. I'm gonna go.
顺便告诉你  所有妈妈都很吓人
All moms are scary, by the way.
快点  儿子
Hurry up, son!
很高兴认识你  安迪的妈妈
It was nice to meet you, Andy's mom.
很高兴认识你  迈克警探
Nice meeting you, Detective Mike.
-再见  迈克  -回头见  安迪
- Bye, Mike. - See you later, Andy.
晚饭不会自己煮好
Dinner ain't gonna cook itself!
妈  你吼我  没必要吧
You're screaming, Ma. Really?
一定要让我出糗吗
Must you embarrass me like that?
妈  你不能那样大喊大叫
Ma, you can't be shouting like that.
我以为你和朋友们出去玩了
I thought you were out with your friends.
为什么不回家去
Why didn't you just come back inside?
肖恩还在吗
Is Shane still there?
不在  他走了
No. He's gone.
走吧  我有东西要给你
Come on, I've got something for you.
是个惊喜
It's a surprise.
闭上眼
Close your eyes.
好了
Okay.
我知道还有几周才到你的生日
I know it's not your birthday for a couple weeks,
不过搬家让人很不好过
but this move has been really tough.
我知道你有点生我的气  所以
And I know you're kinda mad at me, so...
我觉得这是你应得的
I think you deserve this.
惊喜  早来的礼物
Surprise! Early present.
你是在叹气吗
Is that a sigh?
这就是你一直很迷的巴弟啊
That's the Buddi thing you're obsessed with.
是的  只是...
Yeah, um, it's just...
这是给小孩子玩的玩具了
This thing is for, like, little kids now.
一年前就发售了
It came out, like, a year ago.
好吧  我知道这很傻  但我觉得会很有趣的
Okay, I know it's stupid, but I thought it'd be funny.
拜托
Come on!
-试试看  -好吧
- Let's try it. - Okay.
记住  这是翻新的
Just remember, it's refurbished,
所以可能不太好用  好吗
so it might not work perfectly, okay?
巴弟
错误代码57
你的巴弟已连接
Your Buddi is now connected.
酷
Cool.
你好  你是我最好的朋友吗
Hi. Are you my best buddy?
大概吧
I guess?
正在铭记
好刺眼
That's bright.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
安迪  干啥
Andy. 'Sup?
你好  安迪干啥
Hi, Andysup.
-抱歉  -我叫什么名字
- Sorry. - What's my name?
出自《星球大战》系列电影
汉·索洛
Han Solo.
你是说恰吉吗
Did you say Chucky?
什么  不  完全不对
What? No. Not even close.
-恰吉  -是...
- Chucky. - It's...
我喜欢这名字
I like that.
恰吉
Chucky.
我是恰吉
I'm Chucky.
你想做什么  安迪干啥
What do you wanna do, Andysup?
安迪  我就叫安迪
Andy. It's just Andy.
我不知道  做些有意思的事
I don't know. Do something cool.
打开电视吧
I guess turn on the TV.
交给我吧
I will do that.
电视是什么
What's a TV?
你在开玩笑吗  那东西
Are you joking? That thing.
我无法处理这个指令
I cannot process that command.
等一下  这上面说你必须
Wait a minute. It says here you gotta
"将他的知识库云同步"
"sync his knowledge base to the cloud
"他才能和其它卡斯兰产品连接"
"before he can connect to any other Kaslan products."
好吧  恰吉
Okay, Chucky,
连接到云
connect to the cloud.
下载
Download.
学习东西
Learn stuff.
我无法做到
I am unable to do that.
有点诡异
It's kinda creepy.
不能用
Doesn't work.
老天
God.
好吧  这玩意太蠢了
Okay, this thing is stupid.
我不知道它坏成了这样
I didn't know it was that messed up.
-不  妈妈  -我拿回去  没事
- No, Mom. - I'll take it back. It's fine.
妈妈  说实话  我很喜欢
Mom. Mom, honestly, I like it.
-不  你不喜欢  -真的很棒
- No, you don't. - Seriously. It's great.
他很搞笑
He's hilarious.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
其实还挺酷的
It's actually pretty cool.
去睡觉吧  安迪干啥
Go to bed, Andysup.
走吧
Come on.
危险
闲人免进
这是我的房间
This is my room.
那是米奇·鲁尼
And that's Mickey Rooney.
他特别混蛋  所以不要摸他
He's a total dick, so just don't touch him.
特别混蛋
Total dick.
你可以说这词吗
You're allowed to say that?
酷
Cool.
这是我的书桌
This is my desk.
这是我的素描本
This is my sketchbook.
我有时胡乱搭配警察拍档
I do fake buddy cop team-ups sometimes.
比如德古拉和罗宾汉
Like, Dracula and Robin Hood.
或者
Or...
这个是佐罗和美杜莎
This one's Zorro and Medusa.
有点牵强
Kind of a deep cut.
说不好  这很蠢
I don't know, it's stupid.
我不觉得这很蠢
I do not think it's stupid.
谢谢
Thanks.
来自会说话的娃娃的怜悯恭维
Pity compliments from a talking doll.
我的人生啊
That's my life.
今晚就到这里吧
That's enough for tonight.
你想睡觉前唱巴弟之歌吗
Do you want to sing the Buddi song before bed?
不  不用了
No. I'm good.
♪ 你是我的朋友  直到永远 ♪
♪ You are my buddy until the end ♪
♪ 不止是朋友  你是我最好的朋友 ♪
♪ More than a buddy, you're my best friend ♪
好吧  一点都不古怪
Right. Totally not weird at all.
我们玩得开心吗
Are we having fun now?
算是吧
Sure. I guess.
棒
Yay!
好吧
Okay.
又到玩耍时间了吗  我们玩得开心吗
Is it time to play again? Are we having fun now?
不  我们要睡觉
No. We're having sleep.
闭上眼睛好吗  假装不这么吓人
Just please close your eyes and pretend to be less creepy.
你是我最好的朋友  安迪
You're my best friend, Andy.
好  别再这么古怪  该安静了
Okay. Stop being so weird. Quiet time.
♪ 你是我的朋友 ♪
♪ You are my buddy ♪
♪ 直到永远 ♪
♪ Until the end ♪
♪ 不止是朋友  你是我最好的朋友 ♪
♪ More than a buddy, you're my best friend ♪
♪ 我那么爱你  你想象不到 ♪
♪ I love you more than you will ever know ♪
-♪ 我永远不会... ♪  -闭嘴好吗
- ♪ I will never... ♪ - Please shut up.
♪ 离开你 ♪
♪ let you go ♪
晚安  安迪
Good night, Andy.
安迪  你忘了拿你的科学课本
Andy, you forgot your science book.
恰吉  这不是课本
Okay, Chucky, this is not a book.
这些都不是课本
None of these are books.
老实待在这里  好吗
Just stay here, okay?
别再拿课本了
And no more books.
-你回来了  -天啊
- You're back! - Jesus!
你一直等在这里吗
Were you here the whole time?
我给你做了一份礼物
I made you a present.
-一根断木棍  -安迪
- A busted stick. - Andy.
我不明白她看上肖恩哪点了
I don't get what she sees in Shane.
我是说
I mean,
他人不好
he's not nice.
他就是个混蛋
He's just an asshole.
反正也无所谓
It doesn't matter anyway.
最终他也会离开我们
He's just gonna end up leaving us,
就像其他人一样
like everybody else.
我永远不会离开你
I will never leave you.
我们玩得开心吗
Are we having fun now?
算是吧
Yeah. I guess.
-进攻  -你不应该让首领带头
- Attack? - You shouldn't lead with your chieftain.
我还有很多要教你的  好吧
I still have to teach you so much about this. Okay...
好了  又该我掷骰子了
Okay. And I get to roll again. So...
棒  两个六
Boom! Double sixes!
你的兽人出局了
Okay, get that orc outta here.
特别混蛋
Total dick.
说得好
Nailed that one.
-那是什么  -猫抓了我
- What is that? - The cat scratched me.
疼死了
Hurts like hell.
猫咪伤了安迪吗
Kitty hurt Andy?
是的  待在这里  我去找创可贴
Yeah. Stay here. I'm gonna go find a Band-Aid.
蠢鲁尼
Stupid Rooney.
我发誓  我受够了这只猫
I swear, I'm so sick of this cat.
鲁尼  我对天发誓  如果你不闭嘴
Rooney, I swear to God, if you don't shut up,
我就给你换回干猫粮了
I'm putting you back on dry food.
恰吉  住手
Chucky! Stop!
你不能那么做  你为什么要那么做
You can't do that, okay? Why would you do that?
他伤了你  他让你不开心
He was hurting you. He was making you unhappy.
恰吉  听着  看着我
Chucky, okay, listen, look at me.
这很重要
This is important.
你不能伤人  或者猫
You can't hurt people, or cats.
这样不好
It's not cool.
我知道你与众不同  但是
I know you're different, but...
我们必须保密  知道吗
that's gotta be our secret. Okay?
别说古怪的话或者吓唬人
And don't say any weird shit or creep people out.
猫吓坏了
Cat's freakin' out.
把房间收拾干净
Clean up this room.
除了那个家伙
Except maybe that guy.
我有个主意
I've got an idea.
好了  如果要成功
Okay. If this is gonna work,
我需要你的样子
I need you to look as creepy
越诡异吓人愤怒残忍越好  知道吗
and scary and angry and mean as possible. All right?
尽可能睁大你的眼睛  像这样
So, open your eyes as wide as you can, like...
不  你还是很可爱
No, you still look cute.
尽可能张大嘴巴
Open your mouth as wide as you can
呲牙咆哮
and snarl with your lips.
不过像笑一样
But kinda smile.
完美  好  就像这样
Perfect! Okay, yes, just like that.
好  试试这个
Okay. Try this one.
尽可能张大嘴笑
Smile as wide as you can.
更大
Wider.
棒
Yes!
好吧
Yeah...
还真的挺吓人的
It's actually pretty damn creepy.
好了  可以停下了
Okay, you can stop now.
富兰克林  富兰克林
Franklin! Franklin!
见鬼  抱歉
Shit. Sorry.
没事
It's fine.
太他妈吵了
It's fucking loud.
那东西说脏话了
That thing just swore.
它应该不能说脏话的
It... It's not supposed to be able to do that.
是的  我知道  他...
Yeah. I know. He...
它并不遵守规则
It doesn't really follow the rules.
它不遵守规则
It doesn't follow the rules?
就像它能选择一样吗
Like it has a choice?
算是吧
Kinda, yeah.
抱歉  我打断一下  他什么都能做吗
Sorry, can I pop in here? So he just does whatever?
你让他做什么都行吗
You can make him do whatever?
基本上是的
Pretty much.
我能说一句吗
Okay, can I just point out that
所有机器人末日剧情都是这样开始的
this is how every robot apocalypse scenario begins?
-说"包皮垢"  -包皮垢
- Say "dick cheese." - Dick cheese.
真是酷爆了
That is the coolest.
我有好多问题  你是谁
I have so many questions. Who are you?
他叫安迪干啥
His name is Andysup.
-我是安迪  -我是法玲  他是普格
- I'm Andy. - Falyn. Pugg.
你怎么坐在楼道里
Why are you in the hall?
我本来想教他
I was gonna try and teach him
怎么吓唬我妈的男友
to creep out my mom's boyfriend, but
不过这可能是个坏主意
probably a bad idea.
你错了  这主意太棒了
You're wrong. It's perfect.
我们马上就干
And we're doing it right now.
老天  操  妈的...
Jesus! Fuck! Fuckin'...
凯伦
Karen!
-凯伦  -快看啊
- Karen! - Check it out.
-瞧瞧  -天呐
- Look at that. - Oh, my God.
太带劲了
This is legendary.
我们来找安迪
We're here for Andy.
该走了  混球
Let's move, dick turd.
-你们是谁  -法玲和普格
- Who are you? - Falyn and Pugg.
法玲和普格是名字吗
Those are names? Falyn and Pugg?
-准备好了吗  -好了  我晚点回来
- Ready? - Yeah. Be back later!
-你姐姐挺性感  -老兄  那是我妈
- Your sister's pretty hot. - Dude, that's my mom.
更性感了
Even hotter.
你确定那个管理员不会为此发狂吗
You sure the janitor guy is not gonna get any shit for this?
谁在乎啊  那人就是个变态
Who cares? Guy's a total creep.
那玩意坏了吗  怎么看着有点怪
Is that thing busted? It's kinda weird looking.
没有  他只是与众不同
No. He's just different.
现在说  "为了图派克"
Now say, "This is for Tupac!"
被看作有史以来最伟大的说唱歌手
1996年死于枪击
你想唱巴弟之歌吗
Do you wanna sing the Buddi song?
不  说"为了图派克"  然后捅它
No! Say, "This is for Tupac," and stab the asshole.
-快点  -但我想唱
- Come on! - But I want to.
我们想要这视频火起来  他搞什么
We want this to go viral. He for real?
♪ 你是我的朋友... ♪
♪ You are my buddy... ♪
够了
That's enough.
该走了  恰吉
Time to go, Chucky.
缉毒警报  闭嘴  闭嘴
Narc alert. Shut up, shut up.
我居然被他嘲笑了
I just got owned.
该死的千禧小鬼
Little fucking millennials.
1986年电影《德州电锯杀人狂2》
安迪  你想玩耍吗
Andy, you wanna play now?
现在不行  恰吉
Not now, Chucky.
太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
等着
Wait for it.
Wait for it...
收信时间到了
Time for incoming mail!
一  二
One, and a-two...
-小心  贱人  -三
- Heads up, bitch! - ...and a-three!
嘭
Boom!
太棒了
Yes!
看到了吗
Did you see that?
什么鬼  那是什么鬼电影
What the hell? What even is that?
我也不知道  我在商店里买的
I don't know, I bought it at a store.
太假了
It's so unrealistic.
而且具体
And specific.
恐怖电影都是这样的吗
Are all horror movies like this?
-不是  -差不多
- No. - Pretty much.
-是的  没错  -不对  不是
- Yes, they are. - No, they're not.
真恶心  那是他的脸吗
Gross. Is that his face?
什么鬼
What the hell?
你他妈在看吗
Are you fucking watching this?
这根本不现实
That wouldn't even happen.
小心  贱人
Heads up, bitch.
安迪
Andy.
等着
Wait for it.
太精彩了
That is priceless.
小心  贱人
Heads up, bitch.
暂停
-小心  贱人  -恰吉  把刀放下
- Heads up, bitch. - Chucky? Put down the knife.
-小心  贱人  -安迪
- Heads up, bitch. - Andy!
恰吉
Chucky!
停下
Stop!
-你到底怎么回事  -我
- What is wrong with you? - I, uh...
我以为这会让你开心
I thought it would make you happy.
对不起  安迪
I'm sorry, Andy.
我要跟法玲和普格出去
I'm going out with Falyn and Pugg.
我这辈子从没试过烘焙
I have never baked anything in my life before, but
但你看烤出来多漂亮
look how good they look!
我不是很饿
I'm not really hungry.
我再去拿瓶啤酒
I'm gonna grab another beer.
不过看上去真的不错
They do look good though.
好吧
Okay.
很好吃
It's good.
老天
Jesus!
肖恩真是个混蛋
Shane's such an asshole.
肖恩真是个混蛋  真是个混蛋
Shane's such an asshole. Such an asshole.
-你听到了吗  -真是个混蛋
- Do you hear that? - Such an asshole.
肖恩真是个混蛋
Shane's such an asshole.
你开什么玩笑
You gotta be kiddin' me.
肖恩真是个混蛋
Shane's such an asshole.
-肖恩真是个混蛋  -你觉得这很好笑吗
- Shane's such an asshole. - You think that's funny?
真是个混蛋  真是个混蛋
Such an asshole. Such an asshole.
肖恩真是个混蛋
Shane's such an asshole.
我没让他说任何话
I didn't make him say anything!
好吧  你知道吗  你得少跟他在一起玩
Okay. You know what? You're spending less time with this thing.
最多每天一小时
One hour a day, tops.
然后其它时间  他都得待在这里
And the rest of the time, he's going in here.
妈妈  停手  你会吓到他的
Mom, stop, you're gonna scare him!
这是个玩具
It's a toy.
你不必把他也卷进来
You don't have to bring him into this.
这是个玩具  安迪
It's a toy, Andy.
而且他总是吓到鲁尼  好吗
And he keeps freaking out Rooney, okay?
所以我要分开他们
So I'm keeping them separated.
如果他待在我的房间里
I can keep him away from Rooney
就不会跟鲁尼有接触了
if he stays in my room.
必须把他放那里  没得商量
He's staying in there, that is final!
鲁尼
Rooney!
恰吉
Chucky?
是你干的吗
Did you do this?
猫咪让我们不开心  现在我们又可以玩了
Kitty made us unhappy. Now we can play again.
我发誓  我受够了这只猫
I swear, I'm so sick of this cat.
I swear, I'm so sick of this...
我发誓  我受够了这只猫
I swear, I'm so sick of this cat.
垃圾滑槽
不行  绝对不行
No, absolutely not.
二代巴弟发售那天我不会去上班的
I'm not working the Buddi 2 launch.
那天是我孩子的生日
It is my kid's birthday,
而且我也不上夜班了
and I'm not doing night shifts anymore.
你见到鲁尼了吗
Hey, have you seen Rooney?
肖恩没关门  或许他跑出去了
Shane left the door open. Maybe he got out.
为什么没关门
Why is the door being left open?
我们要点披萨外卖
We are ordering pizza.
你饿吗  你想吃什么
You hungry? What do you want?
在听吗  吃披萨
Hello? Pizza.
安迪
Andy.
怎么了
What?
-你要去哪  -普格家
- Where are you going? - Pugg's.
别忘了你的娃娃
Don't forget your little doll.
不想要了
Don't want it.
说真的  我做什么了
Seriously, what did I do?
只要我走进来  他就离开
Every time I walk in a room, he leaves.
根本不是这样
That is not true, at all.
安迪只是有些与众不同  好吗
Andy's just a bit different, okay?
他甚至不能和我共处一室
Kid can't even be in the same room as me.
你是我最最最好的朋友吗
Are you my b-b-b-best buddy?
-混蛋  -天啊
- Asshole. - Oh, Jesus!
肖恩真是个混蛋  肖恩真是个混蛋
Shane's such an asshole. Shane's such an asshole.
该死的
God damn it!
真是个混蛋  真是个混蛋
Such an asshole. Such an asshole.
该死的小鬼
Goddamn kid!
你对我有意见  说出来  明白吗
You got a problem with me, you say it, okay?
别再用你的娃娃了
No more using your little doll.
妈妈
Mom!
坐下
Sit down!
我跟你还没完呢
I'm not through with you.
你对我有意见
Now you got a problem with me,
当个男人  跟我说清楚
you be a man and you say it.
来吧  说来听听
Come on. Let's hear it.
是啊
Yeah.
我就知道你没种
That's what I thought.
我恨他  我恨死他了
I hate him. I hate him so much!
他就不能放过我们吗
Why can't he just leave us alone?
他就不能消失吗
Why can't he just go away?
我只想让他消失
I just want him gone.
我只想让他放过我们
I just wish he would leave us alone.
我只想说他是我儿子
I'm just saying he's my son,
如果你对他有意见的话
so if you have a problem with him,
跟我说  我去跟他谈
talk to me, and then I'll talk to him.
因为你不是他爸爸  而且...
Because you're not his dad and...
行了  我听明白了
Yeah, I get it.
听着  是他很无理我才想教训他
Look, he was being rude, and I called him on it.
我只是觉得有点过火
I just think it's too much.
我只不过跟他说了几句而已
All I did was I talked to him.
-有点过火  没别的  -你知道吗  随便吧
- It's a little much, that's all. - You know what? Fuck it.
听上去是你的问题  不是我的
Sounds like a "you" problem, not a "me" problem.
是的  我知道
Yes, I know.
听着  给我听着
Listen, just listen,
我他妈要发火了  知道吗
I am getting fucking pissed on, okay?
我已经够努力了
I work hard enough as it is,
我不要跟你讲这些废话
and I'm not having this goddamn conversation!
-我的女儿们  -爸爸
- There's my girls! - Daddy!
-天呐  你们长太大了吧  -爸爸  爸爸
- Oh, boy, you guys are so big! - Daddy! Daddy!
该死的圣诞彩灯  挂着别管不行吗
Fucking Christmas lights. Just leave 'em up.
我在家做的还不够多吗
I don't do enough around here?
我他妈应该先把插头拔了
I guess I should've fucking unplugged them first.
见鬼
Oh, fuck!
该死的浣熊
Goddamn raccoons.
滚开
Get out of here!
天啊
Oh, God!
天啊  简  救命
Oh, God! Jane, help!
挠痒痒时间到了
It's tickle time!
简  救命
Jane! Help!
没人能伤害我最好的朋友
Nobody hurts my best buddy!
为了图派克
This is for Tupac.
死者被捅了十三刀
Body was stabbed 13 times.
这双鞋是我刚买的
I just bought these fucking shoes.
指纹采集进展如何
Where we at with print casting?
仅有的家人以外的指纹看起来是幼儿的
Only other prints look to fit a toddler.
他妻子说他下班就直接回家了
Wife says he came here straight home from work.
南部中心社区健身房
肖恩
嗯
Yeah.
我不确定他说的是实话
I'm not sure that's true.
白人死在西瓜田里
White guy dead in a watermelon patch.
"爱吃西瓜"是对黑人的歧视性刻板印象
真有诗意
Poetic.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
惊喜
Surprise!
现在我们又可以玩了
Now we can play again.
什么  什么  为什么
What? What? Why?
我愿意为最好的朋友做任何事
I'd do anything for my best buddy.
什么  不不  我没让你这么做
What? No! No, I didn't want this!
我怎么会想让你这么做
Why would I want this?
天啊
Holy shit!
你为什么要这么做  恰吉
Why would you do this, Chucky?
我只想让他消失
I just want him gone.
我只想让他放过我们
I just wish he would leave us alone.
我只想让他消失
I just want him gone.
-我只想让他放过我们  -不  不  停下
- I just wish he would leave us alone. - No! No, stop!
-停下  -我只想让他消失
- Stop! - I just want him gone.
我只想让他放过我们
I just wish he would leave us alone.
安迪  住手
Andy, stop.
你召唤我们
You beckoned?
出什么问题了
What's the problemo?
他身体的其他部分呢
Where's the rest of him?
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I... I don't know!
他头上有个蝴蝶结
There's a bow on its head.
该死  该死
Shit, shit!
早就有迹象  但是我们袖手旁观
We saw the signs, and we did nothing!
这都是我们的错
This is all our fault.
-早就有迹象  -别再说重复了
- We saw the signs. - Stop saying that!
我该怎么办  我要报警吗
What do I do? Do I call the cops?
-不行  -他死了 我可以告诉他们真相
- No. - He's dead. I can tell them the truth.
告诉他们真相  没问题
Tell them the truth? Sure.
告诉他们一个死人的脸皮
We tell them that a dead guy's face skin
出现在你的房间里
ended up in your room
因为你的玩具变成变态杀手了
because your toy went full-blown psycho killer.
看看这话效果如何
Let's see how that goes.
它在向我眨眼  我不能再看它了
It's winking at me. I can't look at it anymore.
我们得把证据藏起来
We gotta hide the evidence.
藏在哪里
In what?
该死
Shit.
那是脑子吗
Is that brain?
皮肤贴在瓜上
The skin's on a melon.
为什么会有水果
Why is there a fruit involved?
你就径直走去垃圾滑槽
Just go straight to the garbage chute
把它丢进去
and make the drop.
-好  -要是有人拦下你
- Right. - And if anybody stops you,
就说你要拉肚子之类的  没时间说
say you have crazy diarrhea or something, no time to talk.
妈妈
Hi, Mom.
安迪  你怎么没去学校
Hi, Andy. Why are you not in school?
我拉肚子了
Crazy diarrhea.
好  知道了  那是什么
Okay, got it. What is that?
一个礼物
It's a present.
礼物  送给谁的
Present? For who?
送给楼道那头那位老妇人
The old lady down the hall,
因为她给我辅导功课
because she helps me with homework.
-所以我给她做了一个礼物  -真棒
- So, I made her a thing. - Cool.
你们帮他一起做的吗
And you guys helped him with this?
-不  全是他做的  -不  不  不是
- No, it was all him. - No, no, no.
-他自己做的  -对
- It was him. - Yeah.
我们把礼物送过去吧
Let's go deliver it. The present.
什么
What?
多琳
Hi, Doreen.
真是惊喜
Isn't this a surprise!
是啊
I know.
这是给你的
This is for you.
为了感谢你给他辅导功课  对吗
For all of the homework stuff that you helped him with. Right?
好  不客气
Oh, yeah. Of course!
不用谢
Of course, yeah.
很开心能帮助一个如此贴心的男孩
Always happy to help such a sweet boy.
给她吧
Give it to her.
我真是笨手笨脚
Butterfingers over here.
好重啊
It's heavy.
但愿不是易碎品
I hope it's not fragile.
我想知道是什么  拆开吧
I just wanna know what it is. Open it.
好
Yeah.
不  不  别拆开
No! No! Don't! Don't!
下周是我的生日  到时候我们可以一起拆开
My birthday is next week, and we can open it then. Together.
好的  真是个奇特又可爱的想法
Okay, that's a very strange and lovely thought.
那我就把它放到柜子上等待你的生日
So, I'll just go put it on the shelf until then.
-好吗  好  -好
- Okay? Okay. - Okay.
-好了  谢谢你们  -不客气
- All right. Thank you. - No problem.
-多琳...  -再见
- And, Doreen... - Bye.
蠢死了  我们为什么用了礼品包装纸
Stupid! Why did we use wrapping paper?
没关系  没事的  好吗
It's fine. It's fine, okay?
我的生日是下周五  我们还有时间
We have till my birthday, next Friday.
我会搞定的  别担心
I'll get rid of it. Don't worry.
你们在担心那颗头吗
You guys are worried about the head?
你的衣柜里有个杀人娃娃
You've got a killer doll in your closet.
你知道我们该怎么做
And you know what we gotta do.
该死
Shit.
普格
Pugg!
你把我独自留在这里
You left me all alone.
我不喜欢衣柜
I don't like the closet.
我知道  恰吉
I know, Chucky.
把刀放下
Drop the knife.
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best buddy.
我只是想让你开心
I just want you to be happy.
我知道  伙计
I know, buddy.
我们现在就去玩
And we're gonna go play now,
但你得把刀放下  好吗
but you've gotta drop the knife, okay?
走  我们去玩吧
Come on. Let's go play.
来吧
Come on.
来吧  进来
Come on. In here.
我们玩得开心吗
Are we having fun now?
安迪  怎么回事
Andy, what's happening?
快  快  安迪  快动手
Now, now, Andy, now! Now!
安迪
Andy?
为什么要这样做
Why are you doing this?
他们想要伤害我  安迪
They're trying to hurt me, Andy.
他怎么会这么强壮
How is he so strong?
安迪
Andy!
抱歉  恰吉  这是唯一的办法
I'm sorry, Chucky. It's the only way.
但你是我的朋友
But you're my friend!
你在等什么  快动手
What are you waiting for? Do it!
♪ 你是我的朋友  直到永远 ♪
♪ You are my buddy until the end ♪
安迪  快
Andy! Come on.
就这样吧
That's it.
永远不要向任何人说起今晚发生的事
We never talk about what happened tonight to anybody.
中大奖了
Jackpot.
好了
There you are.
连接断了  但整体还行
The connectivity's down, but not in bad shape overall.
只要把你修好  我就能倒卖个好价钱
I'll make a pretty penny on resale once we get you sorted.
该把你拆开了
Time to open you up.
看看有什么毛病
Let's see what we're dealing with.
太愚蠢了
So stupid.
我怎么能这么愚蠢
How could I be so stupid?
我很快回来  好吗  你就待在这里
I'm gonna be right back, okay? Just stay here.
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.
小伙子  别担心  好吗
Hey, man. Don't worry, okay?
我的搭档只是在问她一些常规问题
My partner is just asking her some routine questions.
我爱你
I love you.
好的
Okay.
还需要我提供支援陪你妈妈吃晚饭吗
Still want some backup with your mom for some dinner?
不用了
We're good.
我开玩笑的  进来吧
I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Come on.
这是...好吧
This is... Okay, all right.
-他还不知道这个  -安迪
- He doesn't know about it yet. - Andy?
-不  我要问安迪  -好
- No, I'll just ask Andy. - Sure.
安迪 好
- Andy! - Okay.
我要宣布一件事
I have an announcement to make.
我下载了...
I downloaded...
你们准备好了吗
You ready?
-卡斯兰应用  -好
- The Kaslan app. - Okay.
-卡斯兰专车  -卡斯兰专车
- The Kaslan drive. - Kaslan drive.
我还以为是约会应用  天呐
I thought it was a dating app. Oh, my God.
你太笨了
You are so silly!
你能想象她出去约会吗
Can you imagine if she was out here dating?
怎么了  我很迷人
And so what? I'm desirable.
是我说错话
Excuse me.
安迪  帮我看看这个东西
Anyway, Andy, help me figure this thing out.
好
Okay.
应用在这里  我要怎么做
So, here's the app. What do I do?
好  你注册后  只要按下这个按键
Okay. So, once you sign up... you just press this button
车就会出现在你所在的位置
and the car will show up to wherever you are,
带你去你想去的地方  非常简单
take you wherever you want. It's super easy.
不  等等  它会送我去玩宾果游戏吗
No, wait. It'll drive me to Bingo,
那我就不用让这个笨蛋带我跑东跑西了
and I don't have to worry about this bozo driving me around?
是的
Yeah.
安迪  你是我的新好友
Andy, you're my new best friend.
我不想让你独自出门  好吗
I don't want you going out there alone, okay?
那样不安全
'Cause it's not safe.
这里唯一不安全的就是你的厨艺
The only thing not safe around here is your cooking.
-是吗  因为我...  -是的
- Is that right? 'Cause, um, I can... - Yeah.
-可怜的安迪遭罪了  -吃起来像速食
- Poor Andy gotta suffer... - It tastes like instant!
很好吃  我觉得很好吃
It's good. I think it's good.
-你知道吗  -谢谢你  安迪
- You know what? - Thank you, thank you Andy.
你太为别人着想了  安迪
You are just too sweet for your own good, Andy.
别吃了  别被他影响
That's all. Don't be influenced by him.
我的厨艺是向你学的
I learned my cooking from you, you know?
对  因为我厨艺很好
Yeah, 'cause I can cook.
天呐
Oh, God...
-妈  -怎么了  宝贝
- Hey, Ma. - Yeah, baby.
你又去买古董了吗  我没见过那个
You been to vintage shoppin' again? 'Cause that looks new.
这是安迪给我做的
Andy made this for me.
我们要...
And we are gonna...
我知道  可重了
Yeah, I know. It's heavy.
我们要在他生日那天拆开它
And we are gonna open it on his birthday.
说说看  你上一次给我做东西是什么时候
Tell me, when's the last time you made me anything?
从来没做过
Never.
好吧
Okay.
天呐  妈妈真难搞  对吧
Oh, my God, moms, right?
我知道大家可能一直在跟你说我的事
Look, um... I know that people have probably been talking to you about me,
但别相信你所听到的一切
but, uh, don't believe everything you hear.
这个社区有不少坏影响
You know, this neighborhood has a lot of bad influences.
你懂吗
You know what I mean?
人们喜欢保持沉默
People like to keep their mouth shut.
认为他们需要融入环境
You know, thinking they need to fit in,
但融入并不总是一件好事
but fitting in isn't always a good thing.
你懂吗
You know what I mean?
在这种地方你得谨慎选择一起混的人
Gotta be careful who you hanging around in a place like this.
等你长大一点  就会开始意识到...
When you get a bit older and you start to realize that it's just...
连听力障碍者都不想听我说话
Even the hearing impaired don't wanna listen to me.
真棒
That is fantastic.
你的巴弟已连接
Your Buddi is now connected.
-你好  -太好了
- Hi! - Yes.
你是我最好的朋友吗
Are you my best buddy?
巴弟  你能与卡斯兰的产品连接吧
Buddi, you can connect to Kaslan products, right?
当然可以  你喜欢音乐吗
Sure. Do you like music?
我喜欢
I do, I do.
正在连接卡斯兰音乐
Connecting to Kaslan Music.
太棒了
Yes!
搞定了
There it is.
易趣  我们终于要来了
eBay, here we come. Finally.
卡斯兰  重启系统
Kaslan, system reboot.
您的连接受到干扰
Your connection is experiencing interference.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
卡斯兰  重启系统
Kaslan! System reboot!
Kaslan, system reboot!
巴弟
Buddi?
卡斯兰  开灯
Kaslan, lights on.
卡斯兰
Kaslan.
卡  卡斯兰
Ka... Kaslan?
灯已开启
Lights activated.
卡斯兰  开灯
Kaslan, lights on.
你是什么鬼东西
What the fuck are you?
台锯已启动
Table saw activated.
天啊
Oh, my God.
对不起  天啊  对不起
I'm sorry, God, I'm sorry.
救救我
Please, help me!
调温器达到最高温度
Thermostat reaching maximum temperature.
靠  靠
Shit! Shit!
关掉  关掉  关掉
Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off!
操  操
Fuck! Fuck!
妈的
Oh, shit.
该把你拆开了
Time to open you up.
看看有什么毛病
Let's see what we're dealing with.
警告  设备过热
Warning. Device overheating.
靠  不
Shit! No.
猜猜奥马尔收到了什么
Guess what Omar got.
有人把它放在了他门口
Someone left it outside his door.
我的巴弟是能用的
My Buddi actually works.
我给他取名为屌丝
I named him Chode.
看这个  屌丝
Check this out. Hey, Chode.
向你的主人敬礼
Salute your master.
主人  想去吃汉堡吗
Hey, master. Wanna go get a burger?
很好吃哦
Yum yum.
二代巴弟将会有五种不同的型号
Buddi 2 will be available in five model designs.
其中包括毛绒绒的新朋友  巴弟熊
Including a fuzzy new friend, the Buddi Bear.
奥马尔  看看这个
Yo, Omar, check it out, dude.
天呐
Oh, my God.
新型号都还没发售呢
The new model isn't even out yet,
他们已经开始卖配件了
and they are already selling accessories.
我是亨利·卡斯兰
I'm Henry Kaslan.
当巴弟将你的孩子铭记于心后
When Buddi imprints on your child,
顾客服务
退换处
他将成为孩子终身的朋友
he becomes a best friend for life.
巴弟唯一的使命就是让你的孩子开心
Buddi's only goal is making your child happy.
往后一点  往后一点  好了
Back farther. Back farther. There.
二代巴弟...
The Buddi 2...
安迪
Andy.
-你想玩耍吗  -屌丝  走开
- Do you wanna play now? - Chode, go away.
这可不是对待你最好的朋友的态度
That's no way to treat your best friend.
我们不是朋友
We're not friends.
你这么说我很难过
I'm sorry to hear that.
因为如果我不能做你最好的朋友
Because if I can't be your best buddy,
谁都不能做
then nobody can.
这是你自己说的
You said it yourself.
所有人都会离开你
Everybody leaves you.
你说什么
What did you say?
等着瞧
You'll see.
你对我有意见
You got a problem with me,
说出来  明白吗
you say it, okay?
别再用你的娃娃了
No more using your little doll.
你对我有意见  说出来  明白吗
You got a problem with me, you say it, okay?
别再用你的娃娃了
No more using your little doll.
我只想让他消失
I just want him gone.
我只想让他放过我们
I just wish he would leave us alone.
我只想让他消失
I just want him gone.
我只想让他放过我们  我恨死他了
I just wish he would leave us alone. I fucking hate him!
停下
Stop.
关掉视频
Stop the video.
走开
Go away!
坐下  坐下
Sit down. Sit down.
-我跟你还没完呢  -停下  关掉
- I'm not through with you. - Stop! Turn it off!
坐下  坐下
Sit down. Sit down.
-我跟你还没完呢  -我只想让他消失
- I'm not through with you. - I just want him gone.
停下  关掉  关掉
Stop it! Turn it off! Turn it off!
他就不能放过我们吗
Why can't he just leave us alone?
停下  立刻关掉
Stop! Turn it off! Now!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
-这不是你的巴弟  -不要碰他
- That's not your Buddi. - Don't touch him!
看  看他的眼睛  是红色的
Look! Look at his eyes! They're red!
怎么  你的东西坏了  还想把我的弄坏
What? Your shit breaks, now you gotta bust mine?
这是恰吉  你看他的眼睛
It's Chucky! Look at his eyes!
我说了别碰他
I said don't touch him.
你是聋子吗
You deaf or something?
对了  你就是聋子
That's right. You are.
安迪
Andy!
放开他  别闹了
Get off him, seriously!
听我说
Guys!
这东西是恰吉
That thing is Chucky.
他在控制屏幕
He's controlling the screens.
他是恰吉  看
He's Chucky. Look.
增强现实整合改进了自学技术
AR integration improved self-learning technology.
除此之外
But that's not all.
你有什么毛病
What is wrong with you?
对不起
I'm sorry.
怎么回事  你没事吧
What's going on? Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
过来
Come here.
屌丝  过来  蠢货
Chode, come on, dumbass.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
我以为  我以为他
I thought... I thought he...
安迪  你的助听器呢
Andy, where is your hearing aid?
我来
I got it.
他们找到你的手机了吗
Did they find your phone?
还没有
Not yet.
谢了
Thanks.
巴弟
正在连接
已连接巴弟
我抓到你的把柄了  混蛋
I've got you now, asshole.
-闭嘴  -好吧
- Yo, shut up. - Okay.
还是不敢相信你们和那个变态是朋友
Still can't believe you're friends with that freak.
他不是我们的朋友
He is not our friend.
再也不是了
Not anymore.
-看这个  -好
- Check this out. - Yeah.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
米奇·鲁尼
不  不要现在出问题
No. Not right now.
巴弟
正在缓冲
我要去玩宾果游戏
I'm going to bingo.
你肯定不能走过去
Well, you're sure as hell not walkin' there.
你就不能等到我一会儿下班吗
Why don't you just wait till I get off work in a few?
不用  我叫了专车
No, no. I ordered a car.
我能照顾好自己
I can take care of my own damn self.
系好安全带  拜托
Wear your seatbelt. Please.
巴弟
重新连接
已连接
该死  快点
Oh, shit. Come on.
巴弟
已连接
哎呀呀
My, oh, my.
该死
Oh, shit!
瞧瞧看
Look at this.
卡斯兰专车
A Kaslan Kar.
欢迎乘坐卡斯兰专车
Welcome to Kaslan Kar.
太厉害了
Well, I'll be damned.
请系好您的安全带
Please fasten your seatbelt.
好吧
Okay.
好了  我上车了
Okay, I'm in the car!
我该怎么...
How do I...
我们出发前往您的目的地
We are now on route to your destination.
天  我的天啊
Oh, my. Oh, my goodness.
它在倒车
It's going backwards.
多琳
Doreen!
-安迪  -不
- Hey, Andy. - No!
-瞧瞧这个啊  -停车
- Will you look at this? - Stop the car!
宾果游戏
我们已到达您的目的地
We are now reaching your destination.
快看我坐的车
Hey, look at my ride.
是多琳
It's Doreen!
不要嫉妒我
Don't be jealous now.
卡斯兰
好了  不不  等等
Okay. Oh, no. No, no, wait!
这就是我的目的地
This is my stop!
停车  拜托
Pull over, please!
很抱歉  我听不懂
I'm sorry. I do not understand.
不不不
No! No! No!
不
No!
没人能偷走我的朋友
Nobody steals my friend.
老天  救命
Help me, Jesus!
安迪是我最好的朋友
Andy's my best friend.
你个狗娘养的小矮子
You hobbit motherfucker!
-副驾驶安全气囊已关闭  -等等
- Passenger airbag has been turned off. - Wait!
安全带已解开
Seatbelt disengaged.
小心  贱人
Heads up, bitch.
不要
Please!
您已到达您的目的地
You have arrived at your destination.
我看到你了
I see you.
躲猫猫
Peekaboo.
多琳
Doreen...
我说了  "躲猫猫"
I said, "Peekaboo!"
我在外面看到多琳了
I saw Doreen outside.
妈妈  我觉得恰吉对她做了什么
Mom, I think Chucky did something to her.
亲爱的
Sweetie...
恰吉是个玩具
Chucky is a toy.
好吗  而且已经坏了
Okay? It broke.
-你把它扔掉了  -没有  妈妈
- You got rid of it. - No, Mom.
我看到他了  我看到他跟着多琳
I... I saw him. I saw him following Doreen.
你没看到  听听你自己在说什么
No, you didn't. Listen to what you're saying.
妈妈  他要杀了多琳
Mom, he's gonna kill her!
他可能已经把多琳杀了
He probably already did kill her!
你为什么要这样
Why are you doing this?
拜托  跟我说实话吧
Please, just be honest with me
告诉我鲁尼发生什么了
and tell me what happened to Rooney.
是恰吉干的
It was Chucky!
-恰吉  -为什么你不听我说
- Chucky? - Why aren't you listening to me?
我在奥马尔的手机上看到的
I have it on Omar's phone.
他在跟踪多琳  我可以给你看
He's following Doreen. I can show you.
你怎么会有奥马尔的手机
Why do you have Omar's phone?
我拿的
I took it.
为什么
Why?
我不得不拿  我...
I had to. I...
我必须盯着恰吉  妈妈
I had to follow Chucky, Mom.
好吧
Okay.
我没疯  妈妈
I'm not crazy, Mom!
我要把这个还给奥马尔
I'm giving this back to him.
妈妈  没人肯听我说  求你了
Mom, no one's listening to me. Please.
我得把这个还给他
I have to give this back to him
免得事情变得更糟
so this doesn't get any worse.
没人肯听我说
Nobody's listening to me!
-你乖乖待在这里  好吗  -妈妈
- Just stay right here, okay? - Mom!
然后你要跟我一起去上班
And you're coming to work with me.
他要杀了我们
He's trying to kill us!
待着别动
Do not move.
靠  靠
Oh, shit. Shit.
你不能肯定
You don't know that.
我们不了解这孩子  他可能是个疯子
We barely know this kid. He could be batshit crazy.
要是恰吉根本没出过故障呢
What if Chucky never malfunctioned?
都是他  都是他编造出来的
He just... He just made it all up?
-要是他杀了...  -闭嘴
- What if he killed... - Shut up.
我一直看着他们  安迪
I've watched them, Andy.
我知道他们是怎么伤害你的
I've seen how they hurt you.
在这边  安迪
Over here, Andy!
离我远点
Leave me alone!
在这边
Over here.
不让我们一起玩
If they don't let us play,
他们都得消失
they all go away.
你为什么要这样
Why are you doing this?
我们玩得开心吗
Are we having fun now?
你是我最好的朋友吗
Are you my best buddy?
不让我们一起玩
If they don't let us play,
他们都得消失
they all go away.
躲猫猫
Peekaboo.
停下
Stop!
关掉
Turn it off!
即使今晚可能降雨
But the chance of rain tonight
也无法阻挡巴弟粉丝的热情
won't dampen the spirits of Buddi fans,
泽德商超
因为此刻他们期待已久
as this is the night they have been waiting for.
没错  人们都排着队
That's right, people have been lining up
等待午夜二代巴弟的发售
for the midnight release of Buddi 2.
二代巴弟
所有人员  所有人员
All units. All units,
请注意死者是一名非裔女性  七十多岁
be advised that the deceased is an African American female in her 70s.
收到
Ten-four.
女士  你还好吗
Ma'am, you okay?
是多琳
It's Doreen.
我觉得她死了  到处都是警察
I think she's dead. There are cops everywhere.
如果恰吉真的...
What if Chucky's...
如果安迪是对的呢
What if Andy is right?
你想怎样
The hell you want?
奥马尔  给我们看看你的巴弟
Omar, show us your Buddi.
弄丢了
It's gone.
-操  -什么时候丢的  在哪丢的
- Fuck! - Since when? Where is it?
不如你们去问问安迪
Why don't you ask Andy?
那个混蛋总是偷我的东西
That asshole's been taking my shit.
手机拿来
Give me your phone.
你要把手机也偷走吗
Are you gonna steal it, too?
快点  手机拿来
Give me your phone now.
巴弟
你最好的朋友
相册  直播
正在连接
卡斯兰专车
A Kaslan car.
搞什么
What the hell?
不是吧
No.
天啊
Holy shit.
他是对的
He was right.
安迪
Andy.
可算找到你了
There you are.
记得那个纪念品吗  剥下的脸皮
Remember the souvenir? Skinned face?
找到了
They found it.
今早一个老头从垃圾桶里翻到了
Old man dug it up in a dumpster this morning.
挺不错吧  包得像个礼物一样
Nice, right? Wrapped up like a present.
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
什么破工作
Fuck my job.
该死的头套
Fuckin' thing.
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟
Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi!
快点  我们得带你离开
Come on. We need to get you out of here.
是恰吉  他在这儿
It's Chucky. He's here.
我得去找我妈妈
I gotta find my mom.
-巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  巴弟  -妈妈
- Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! Buddi! - Mom!
过来  给我趴下
Come here! Get the fuck down.
别动  安迪
Now stay down, Andy.
十  九  八...
Ten, nine, eight...
你干什么
What are you doing?
放开他
Get off of him!
恰吉在这儿  他会杀了你的
Chucky's here! He's gonna kill you!
二  一
...two, one!
小心点  该死
Be careful, goddamn it!
怎么回事  迈克
What is going on? Mike!
我不用对你交代任何事  凯伦
Look, I don't have to tell you shit, Karen.
这是我儿子  懂吗
That is my son, okay?
我才不管他是不是你儿子呢
I don't give a fuck that it's your son.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎大家的新好友
say hello to your new best friend.
全新二代巴弟
The all new Buddi 2!
好了  过来
All right, come on.
小心  让开点
Watch out. Move out of the way.
-手拿来  -你必须相信我
- Give me your hand. - You have to believe me.
-有必要这样吗  -妈妈
- Is that necessary? - Mom.
当然有必要
Yeah, it's fucking necessary.
待着别动
Stay put.
我发誓  他会杀了我们的
I promise you, he's gonna kill us.
让我过去  让开  让开
Let me through! Move, move, move!
都让开  快点
Clear a path, come on!
没事的
It's gonna be all right.
看着我  压住伤口  好吗
Look at me. Keep pressure on it, okay?
-快叫医生  -我们必须马上离开
- Somebody call a doctor! - We have to leave right now.
-冷静下来  -不不不  妈妈
- Calm down. Okay? - No, no, no! Mom...
叫医生
Call a doctor!
该死
Oh, shit.
妈妈  你要去哪
Mom, where are you going?
巴弟
正在连接
大家好  我是亨利...
Hello, my name is Henry...
我是亨利·卡斯兰
My name is Henry Kaslan.
欢迎光临你附近的泽德商超
Welcome to your local Zed Mart.
很荣幸向大家介绍...
With great pleasure, I introduce you...
不仅是娱乐
More than just entertainment.
我们的创造更加特别
We created something far more special.
每个孩子都对我们至关重要
Every child is important to us.
而每个孩子都应该有个伙伴
And every child deserves a companion.
一个永远不会让你失望的朋友
A friend that will never let you down.
我们太迟了
We're too late.
-是时候...  -玩耍了
- It's time to... - Play.
趴着别动  明白吗
Stay down, okay?
启动封锁
Lockdown activated.
我无处不在  安迪
I'm everywhere, Andy.
你再也无法摆脱我了
You can't run away from me now.
看到没  他们都离你而去
See? They're all leaving you.
只有我不会
But not me.
这边  我知道出口
This way! I know the way out!
不
No.
操
Fuck!
快跑
Run.
安迪
Andy!
我的天啊
Holy shit!
好的  好的  好的
Okay. Okay! Okay.
安迪呢
Where is Andy?
天啊  救命  救命
Oh, God, help me! Help me!
立刻离开
Exit now.
躲开
Duck!
你没事吧
You okay?
我要跟着她
I'm gonna follow her.
我也是
Me too.
是啊
Yeah.
快点
Come on.
你要去哪  安迪
Where you going, Andy?
妈妈
Mom.
安迪  他是想引我们回去
Andy, he's trying to lure us back in.
我不能就这么丢下她
I can't just leave her there.
如果我们不走  我们全都会死
If we stay, we all die, okay?
我们必须离开
We gotta go!
我们可以报警  安迪
We'll call the cops, Andy.
好吧  好吧  你说得对  我们走
Okay. Okay, you're right. Let's go.
好  好  快走
Okay. Okay, come on.
安迪
Andy!
-发生这些事全都是我的错  -安迪
- It's my fault all this happened, okay? - Andy.
我不能连累你们受伤
I can't let you guys get hurt.
-安迪  别这样  -不  安迪 不
- Andy! Come on! - No! Andy, don't!
-安迪  -安迪
- Andy! - Andy!
-安迪  求你了  -他会杀了你的  安迪
- Andy, please! - He'll kill you, Andy!
好了  恰吉  你想玩耍吗
All right, Chucky, you wanna play?
我们来玩吧
Let's play.
接近了
Getting closer.
不管死活  你都得跟我走
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
妈妈
Mom!
安迪只是有些与众不同
Andy's just a bit different.
闭嘴
Shut up!
你不明白吗
Don't you see?
她不是你的朋友
She's not your friend.
你不需要其他朋友
You don't need other friends.
他们想拆散我们
They try to keep us apart.
想破坏我们的乐趣
Try to ruin our fun.
但我不会让他们得逞
But I won't let that happen.
一切很快就会结束
It will be all over soon.
别担心  安迪
Don't worry, Andy.
她死了之后  你会感谢我的
You're gonna thank me when she's gone.
所有人都死了之后
When they're all gone.
你猜怎么着  安迪
Guess what, Andy?
现在只剩下你和我
Now it's going to be you and me...
永远在一起
forever.
我之前坏了  安迪
I was broken, Andy.
我无法让你开心
I couldn't make you smile.
但我现在被修好了
But I'm better now.
我知道如何让你开心了
I know how to make you happy now.
或许你就是不想开心
Maybe you don't wanna be happy.
或许你也坏了
Maybe you're broken too.
或许我需要拆开你
Maybe I need to open you up,
看看有什么毛病
see what we're dealing with.
我会修好你的  安迪
I'm gonna fix you, Andy.
♪ 你是我的朋友  直到永远 ♪
♪ You are my buddy until the end ♪
什么  安迪
What? Andy?
♪ 不止是朋友  你是我最好的朋友 ♪
♪ More than a buddy, you're my best friend ♪
妈妈
Mom!
我们太迟了
We're too late.
太迟了  太迟了
We're too late. We're too late.
你在破坏我们的乐趣  安迪
You are ruining our fun, Andy!
放开我
Get off!
现在你要和我一起玩了
You're gonna play with me now.
只和我
Only me!
安迪...
Andy...
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were friends.
♪ 你是我的朋... ♪
♪ You are my bu... ♪
-妈妈  -♪ 你是我的朋... ♪
- Mom? - ♪ You are my bu... ♪
♪ 你是我的朋友 ♪
♪ You are my buddy ♪
♪ 直到永远 ♪
♪ Until the end! ♪
永远到此为止
This is the end.
别招惹我儿子
Don't fuck with my son!
妈妈
Mom.
天啊  你没事吧
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
-我没事  -好的
- Yeah. I'm fine. - Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们的调查结果显示卡斯兰对此次发生在
Our investigation has concluded that Kaslan shares no responsibility
泽德商超的悲惨事件不承担任何责任
for the horrific events that transpired at Zed Mart.
不过为了以防万一
However, as a precaution,
我们暂时召回所有二代巴弟产品
we are recalling all Buddi 2 products for the time being.
在卡斯兰  顾客至上
At Kaslan, the customers come first.
我们相信每个孩子都应该有一个终身的朋友
We believe that every child deserves a friend for life.
一个永远不会离开他们的朋友
A friend who will never, ever leave them.
一个朋友
A friend...
直到永远
till the end.